One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Inherited will...
the tides of time,
and humanity's dreams...
They cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Alubarna Palace
T-Terrible news, Commander Chaka!
It's His Majesty!
What?! What are you saying?!
He vanished!
Rebellion
That's absurd!
Have you searched everywhere?!
Yes! Not only the palace,
but the gardens and storehouses as well!
Did he leave in
the middle of the night?
Not possible.
The king's security is top-notch;
nothing escapes our eyes!
Then... Then, why?
Why would the king be absent
at the cusp of battle?!
Find him! Search beyond
the palace walls and in the towns!
Yes, sir!
Pell excels in finding people,
but unfortunately he's busy
scouting out Rainbase.
What has happened to His Majesty?
I can't afford to act recklessly...
Damn it!
Terrible news, Commander Chaka!
It's His Majesty!
What is it?!
Did you find him?!
Yes, sir! It seems he's in Nanohana.
This information is reliable.
I see! That's a relief!
But... But...
Unbelievably enough...
C-Come again?!
Koza!
Wait!
We're coming too!
Why now, all of a sudden?!
How much farther can he fall?!
Don't hold to suspicion, Koza.
Why would he act
so nonsensically?!
You know His Majesty's
character very well.
All you old people say that.
I didn't follow you here to
Yuba for the king's sake.
The Rebel Army is over
100,000 strong now!
Yeah, I heard.
Apparently there've been casualties, too...
It's nothing.
A little rain ought to clear away
his strange suspicions. Yes...
What on earth?!
The canal's been destroyed!
Who would do this?!
Now the water won't
make it into town!
It hasn't rained
for over a year now!
Erumalu is done for!
Don't hold to suspicion, Koza...
I don't want to suspect you,
but people are dying of thirst!
You may not be using it,
but you do have it!
No. Wait for natural rain.
Dance powder summons misfortune.
Just a little won't hurt anything!
Even the smallest amount
of rain might end the rebellion!
Its use would only cascade into calamity.
Using it isn't so easy
an undertaking, Koza.
I can't just sit by... and watch
as our towns dry up anymore!
All this time, and you
have not changed a bit.
I have changed.
I can fight.
I'm... going to...
I'm going to come here...
and I'll take your rain!
Nanohana
Y-Your Majesty?
What did you just say?
Just as you heard.
I am honestly apologizing.
It was I, Cobra, the king of Arabasta,
who stole this country's rain!
Your Majesty Cobra...
This is a joke, right?
It has to be...
It is no joke.
This is crazy...
You only helped yourself
when you know how we suffer?!
That's far too selfish,
even for you, sire!
How dare you, a mere cretin,
talk back to me, the king?
I've come to Nanohana to
apologize for what I've done.
What more do you want?
My brother died in Yuba, you know...
There is another reason I came
all the way out to this city.
As you know, dance powder is
outlawed by the World Government.
If the outside world
learns of its use,
Navy Headquarters will take
action and destroy our country.
This must be avoided.
However, please remember;
we found large batches of dance powder
being smuggled into this town two years ago.
It is necessary to eliminate
all traces of that incident.
You understand, do you not?
You don't mean...
That's right! If we are to be rid
of that terrible incident forever,
we must be rid of this city and all of you!
Wh-What?!
That's insane!
You're ordering us to die?!
Hey! King!
So it was all your fault!
It's...
It's because of you...
You steal the rain and make
all the towns dry up, you jerk!
I'm gonna get you back
for everyone...!
Don't!
Sire...
Men! Burn Nanohana to the ground!
Yes, sire!
Koza!
Koza. It's been a while.
What the hell...
do you think you're doing?
Hey, King!
Stop!
I came to apologize,
as you can see.
Quit screwing around!
Shut up!
Do you realize what you're saying?!
How insulting this is?!
I am the one who's been
using dance powder to–
I said shut up!
Why are you so angry?
Koza...
Surely even you can appreciate...
Sire...
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
...that I...
You asshole!
Do you know how the people felt
as they died off in dried-up towns?!
They never succumbed
to malice or anger for you!
"It isn't the king's fault"!
"He's a great person"!
Ever faithful, that's what they said,
even as they lay there dying.
At least have the decency
to keep lying about your innocence!
How are they supposed to feel about this?!
Koza!
Leader!
Well, I guess it's time!
Didn't... Didn't we fight because...
the kingdom...
no, everyone...
wanted to know that answer?!
At the very least...
that's why I fought...
You can't be serious!
Here they come!
A giant ship is about to crash! Run!
What is that ship?!
Mommy!
I-It's toppling over!
For a final operation,
we barely lifted a finger.
Have any of our assignments
ever been a challenge to us?
That's a wrap!
Now, light the fires
so we can skedaddle!
Yes, sir!
I just can't feel relaxed
without this on!
Koza! Say something!
Koza! Hey!
The Royal Army disappeared!
What?!
How deux you
like my kingliness?!
That was great,
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
Put out the fires!
The damn Royal Army lit fires and ran off!
Hurry!
Put out the fires!
Now to meet up
with Mr. 2 outside town.
Alubarna's the finale.
Hm.
I look forward to it.
Iffy! My favorite word is "iffy"!
Because now it's iffy
whether the king remains king!
The operation's a success!
Where's Bunchi?!
He's to the west of town,
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
Huh? The king turned
into a weird ballerina...
It's no use! It won't go out!
Damn the king!
He was a fake!
This is bad!
Everyone's being tricked!
I have to hurry and tell 'em!
What a naughty little boy.
What do you think he's discovered?
That imbecile was
careless and slipped up.
Who're you?!
I take it there's no use
in asking you to stay quiet.
Water! We need more water!
Wait! That's for my shop!
Can you pay for it?!
Not now, you idiot! The town is on fire!
Put out the fires!
Water!
It's no use. We can't
outpace the fire...
We should probably run for it.
Hang in there, Koza!
You're not the type to die like this!
Hey! Take Koza!
Little boy! Say something!
This is terrible!
Not even children are safe!
I-It's not...
What's that?! I'll stop
the bleeding! Don't talk!
It's not what you think!
Everyone's being tricked!
Hang in there, kid!
Koza!
This country...
Let's end it.
Contact all of our branches!
This will be our final battle!
O-Okay, but we don't
have nearly enough weapons!
No, we do now.
That ship that just crashed?
It was a seafaring armory.
Seriously?!
Yeah! It was full of weapons!
It's almost like... divine providence.
Oh, yeah? Some pipsqueak
spotted me? Swan-swan!
Goodness... Now Mr. 4's team
just needs to do its thing.
Fatty and the old hag
know how to get things done!
Kidnapping the king
will be a walk in the park for them!
Hear me, Rebel Army!
The Arabasta of old is long dead!
This is the final battle!
We're going to capture Alubarna!
We're going to launch an all-out assault!
The king must pay!
We'll build a new country!
Meanwhile, at Alubarna Palace
Nonsense!
His Majesty Cobra would never do such a thing!
It must be a mistake!
But...
his disappearance and
subsequent arrival line up!
He no longer has an alibi!
All of Arabasta knows of
the Nanohana incident,
moving rebels everywhere to action!
And what's more...
the citizens' faith in His Majesty
has turned to hatred;
they're now arming themselves.
Their numbers are unknown!
The entire country is enraged
and headed for Alubarna.
And now...
there's no stopping this.
Please, make your decision!
We will obey you!
How can this be?!
Even the king's words
from yesterday are blurred now!
In what do I put my trust?!
Very well! We need only
fulfill our given duties!
We are the Kingdom of Arabasta's
royal guards!
No country should crumble
in the absence of its king!
Protect the truth you see before you!
Protect this country!
Counter the Rebel Army!
Rainbase
What a horrifying plan...
Well? Do you like it?
The operation you once
participated in has now blossomed.
If you listen closely, you can
probably hear the howls of Arabasta.
They're all thinking the same thing:
"Protect Arabasta."
"Protect Arabasta. Protect Arabas–"
Stop it!
How can you be so cruel?!
Isn't it just heartrending?
Love for this country
is what will lead to its destruction.
Is he stupid?
Or did he not
hear what I said?
He's definitely stupid. But...
that's also why he's our captain.
I've made so many moves
to make it as far as I have:
the sabotage to instigate the citizens;
directing the Royal Army's
misconduct...
Have you any idea why I'd go to
such lengths to attain this country?
There's no deciphering
what's in your desiccated head!
Your tongue is
as sharp as ever, Princess.
Vivi!
Now, now. What are you
trying to do, Miss Wednesday?
Stop you!
I'm going to stop you!
There's still time!
If I can just get to Alubarna east of here...
If I can get there
before the Rebel Army,
I may be able to stop them!
I absolutely refuse...
to let you have your way!
Vivi!
The Rebel Army is
quickly approaching!
Listen! We must protect
Arabasta with our own hands!
Sacrifice is met with bravery!
Face your foe with all your might!
Counter the Rebel Army!
Get in position to intercept!
Topple Alubarna!
Are you okay, Koza?
This is nothing!
At this pace, we'll reach
Alubarna by morning!
Keep up our march
at this speed!
Right!
The decisive battle...
will be at dawn!
What a coincidence.
We're just about
to head to Alubarna too.
If you'd like to come with us, then do so.
Or...
would you rather save these people?
That's–
The key to this cell?!
Give it here!
A hole?!
It won't be too long before
their fight to the death begins.
Even if you hurried to Alubarna from here,
who knows if you'd
make it in time?
To stop the rebellion,
you'd need to leave at once,
Miss Wednesday.
Or will you save these people instead?
Although,
I just inconveniently
dropped the key below the floor...
and into the bananagators' den.
A bananagator!
Bananagator?
Whoa! What's that?!
An alligator's growing
from that banana!
Wh-What is that
insanely huge alligator?!
This room is underwater?!
What a weird banana!
You idiot! Look closer!
It's an alligator with a banana
growing out of it! It's a weird gator!
Hey...! What happened, Vivi?!
A bananagator swallowed
the key to your cell!
What?! Go and make it
spit it out!
That would be impossible!
Bananagators are so ferocious
that they even prey on sea kings!
Get near one,
and they eat you in one bite!
I apologize for clumsily
dropping the key.
Plus, there's no telling
which one swallowed it.
What?!
I can't believe this guy!
Damn! If we could just get out of here,
I'd gut those reptiles!
You're so dumb, Zoro!
We can't get out because
the key got eaten!
I know that!
Well, then.
We must be going
a little earlier than you.
Also, this room
will automatically
get wiped out
in one hour's time.
This secret underground room
I once used
as Baroque Works' president
is no longer necessary.
It will soon fill with water and
be submerged in Rainbase's lake.
One million innocent citizens,
or a mere four pirates
with no future?
You must choose who to save,
though the odds are low for both.
Your feelings are your ante,
Miss Wednesday.
Do you enjoy gambling?
The fools living in this country
made this job so much easier.
The juvenile rebels and the old man
digging in Yuba, for example.
Wh-What?! You mean the dry old guy?!
A foolish old man who keeps
pecking away every day
at an oasis that's long dead.
So many sandstorms come his way,
yet he just keeps at it.
Why, you...!
Tell me, Straw Hat Luffy.
Isn't it odd that sandstorms
keep hitting the same towns
so precisely, time after time?
What are you saying?
Yuba, you see...
can't be beaten by
some lousy sandstorms!
I'll dig it back up as
many times as it takes!
As many times as it takes!
As many times as it takes...
You're the one...
who caused it?!
Vivi-chan.
I have faith in His Majesty!
His character makes him incapable
of betraying his own country.
I-I'll kill you!
Water's leaking in!
The whole room's gonna be
flooded before too long!
Vivi! Help! Do something!
I don't want only
one hour to live!
Quit freaking out.
Really, Zoro?! How can I not freak out at a time like this?!
We'll die if we just sit here!
Don't you understand?!
The country...
or my friends, you say?!
I doubt you really plan
on giving anything back!
You plan to take my life, too,
before I reach Alubarna!
I know full well...
that nothing will end
unless I beat you!
You don't know the first thing...
about this country's people,
history, way of life...
You don't know
anything about it!
Vivi!
Do something!
Get us out of here!
Luffy...
Finally starting to beg
for your life, Straw Hat Luffy?
But it's only natural.
Everyone is afraid of dying.
If we...
If we die, then who's
gonna kick your ass?!
Don't flatter yourself,
small-timer.
You're the "small-timer"!
Well, this is your chance to
abandon them, Miss Wednesday.
If you wish to stop the rebellion, that is.
It's... so big!
Alright! Beat it, Vivi!
That's crazy talk!
It's too huge!
Vivi! Run! You can't
beat it! But help us!
You're the one
who's talking crazy!
Wait! Look out the windows!
They're all waiting
for their turn!
They see us as food!
We're all gonna be in their
stomachs in an hour?!
Peacock Str–
I-It's fast!
That chomp made quick work
of those stairs!
What a jaw!
Vivi!
Damn! These monsters
are unstoppable!
Ow...
Vivi! Run!
Get up!
Vivi! It's gonna eat you!
Someone's calling.
What?
Hello? Hello?
Can you hear me?
Yes, I hear you.
From the millions, right?
Hey, does this thing work?
I've never used a
baby transponder snail before.
Yes, everything is fine.
You can talk just as you are.
What do you want?
Huh?
Just spit out your report!
What happened?
Oh, I've heard
that voice before.
Hm?
Hey there!
You've reached The Shit Shack.
The Shit Shack?
Oh? It sounds like
you remember me. Fantastic.
Hey there!
You've reached The Shit Shack.
Making a reservation?
Quit fooling around, you idiot.
Transponder snail?
Wh-What do you mean?
I never used a transponder snail
while on Little Garden.
I'm certain we have all four
Straw Hat pirates inside that cell.
All that's left is their pet.
Does this mean
there are still others?
Hey, did you hear that?
"The Shit Shack?" Could it be...?
San–
Wait, Luffy!
The enemy doesn't
know about him!
He was in his room when Mr. 2
showed up, so they never met!
Sanji...
That's right!
Sanji and Tony are still outside!
Tell me...
just who the hell are you?
Me? I'm...
Mr. Prince.
I see. Mr. Prince.
Where are you?
'Fraid I can't say!
If I did, you'd come get rid of me.
Though, setting aside whether you can actually get rid of me,
I'm not so stupid as to
divulge information so easily.
Unlike you, Mr. 0.
Prince! Help! We've been caught!
There's no time!
Come rescue me!
Mr. Prince! Help me!
Sounds like my crew's right by your side.
In that case, I'm gonna–
Troublesome bastard!
Hello?
We've caught him! What should
we do with this strange man?!
Sanji... No...
Where are you? Tell me!
Th-The front gate of a casino
in Rainbase named Rain Dinners!
That useless moron!
That bastard better be alive!
Sanji!
Our hope...
This is great.
Let's go to the front gate.
Is that wise? The millions
still don't know who their boss is.
I won't be going as their boss.
Aside from the number agents,
no one knows who you and I are.
What's so strange about Crocodile,
the owner of this casino,
going to see what has happened
in front of his building?
Vivi!
What are you doing, Vivi?!
There's still time before
this room fills up with water!
I'm going outside to get help!
Yeah! There's no way he
kicked the bucket just now!
If Vivi can just free him...
And Chopper's outside too!
We might have a chance!
Look out, Vivi!
Vivi!
Enough of your nonsense!
Vivi! Wake up! Vivi!
The gator's coming! Vivi!
If you love your friends that much,
you can all die here together.
The water will turn this place
into a feeding ground
and submerge the entire room.
I'll drag your cheeky Mr. Prince
here too, if you'd like!
Hopefully you
don't mind corpses!
Damn it!
Oh! Owner Crocodile!
Have you heard
what happened in Nanohana?!
Yes, I have.
The whole town
—no, the whole country—
is clamoring at the news that
the Rebel Army and the Royal Army
are finally about to clash!
I'm not surprised.
The king does let pirates
attack cities freely.
I always thought something
like this might happen.
Hey, look! It's Sir Crocodile!
It really is him!
He's so wonderful!
He rarely shows himself inside the casino!
Sir Crocodile!
You're as popular as ever.
Vivi!
Th-They've always been there....
to help me all this time!
I refuse to just let them die!
Yes! She got away!
The water's broken through the glass!
Now we got less than 20 minutes
until this room's submerged!
Vivi! You alright?!
Everyone! Hang in there a little longer!
I will bring back help!
I promise I won't abandon you!
Yeah! We're counting on you, Vivi!
What in the world...
is this?
Including the employees
who Pell the Falcon just took out,
it looks like all the millions
in this town have been wiped out.
What happened?! Hey!
A-A man named Mr. Prince...
I thought you caught him?
Where did he go?!
He just now headed to
the south part of town...
Just now?
Him?!
You little punk!
Don't think you can escape me.
Why not forget about him?
Quiet. I've always killed everyone
who makes a
laughing stock out of me!
Whoa! An earthquake?!
This is bad! The bridge into
Rain Dinners has collapsed!
Just out of the blue?!
What's going on?!
What caused it?!
Hey! What's going on?!
Now we can't get back to town!
Aren't there any boats?!
What's going on?!
The bridge fell!
Oh no! I can't go outside now?!
It's not for going outside.
It's about keeping Baroque Works
from coming back in.
It's all part of the plan.
Chopper's running around town
as a decoy while we speak.
We gotta hurry.
The rebellion's begun, too.
Sanji!
Think you could tell me
where they are, Princess?